# YANNI ABI

#### WEB DEVELOPER

India | +91 90369 27671 | My portfolio





#### SUMMARY

Experienced Technology Consultant transitioning to a dynamic role as a Web Developer. Proficient at diagnosing a wide range of hardware and software solution-related issues, and now applying these skills to create exceptional web solutions. An excellent team player with a strong focus on client and stakeholder interactions.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

# LIT Infotech | Remote

Web Developer

July 2023 to Present

Specializing in front-end development for web applications leveraging MERN stack, with a primary focus on enhancing navigation, optimizing forms, and elevating overall user experience.

## Hewlett-Packard Enterprise, Bangalore | Bangalore, India

Technology Consultant - Emerging Technologies

August 2022 to June 2023

- Deployed and tailored Kubernetes-based clusters both on-premise and on the cloud.
- Produced feasibility reports, collaborating with stakeholders to tailor container platforms to customer needs.
- Developed and documented installation procedures, ensuring rigorous testing before deployment.
- Delivered expert assistance in monitoring HPE Ezmeral and Data Fabric for clients.
- Diagnosed and resolved container platform configuration issues by collaborating with third-party support.
- Daily Kubernetes cluster monitoring, generating health-check reports and addressed discrepancies.

### Hewlett-Packard Enterprise | Bangalore, India

CIN Specialist

January 2021 to July 2022

- Resolved intricate hardware and software issues related to network virtualization interconnects, pass-through modules, and hardware-software monitoring platforms by performing deep-dive analysis including platform support for the virtualization software.
- Analyzed diverse hardware and software logs to pinpoint root causes, leveraging extensive knowledge base resources to implement optimal solutions.
- Partnered with Engineering and Development teams to expedite resolutions for complex cases to collaborate quarterly and monthly reports.
- Acted as a single point of contact (SPOC) for facilitating communication between Accounts, Engineering, and Support Teams.

• Conducted comprehensive training sessions for new Engineers, covering both technology and process aspects.

## Netconnect Global Pvt Ltd. | Bangalore, India

Technical Solutions Consultant

June 2019 to December 2020

Diagnosed and resolved hardware and software issues related to HPE Industrial Standard Servers, chassis, pass-through modules, and UPS.

# HP Inc. | Bangalore, India

Technical Support Engineer

June 2017 to May 2019

Effectively resolved issues pertaining to a wide range of commercial HP hardware products, including Workstations, Notebooks, and Desktops.

### EDUCATION

Kristu Jayanti College | Bangalore, India

Bachelor in Computer Applications

June 2014 to May 2017

### LANGUAGES & TECHNOLOGIES

Languages/Frameworks: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, React.js, Express.js, Node.js,

MongoDB, SQL, Python

Tools: VS code, Eclipse, Microsoft SQL Server

Technologies/Platforms: RedHat OpenShift, HPE Ezmeral Runtime, Suse Rancher, Vanilla

Kubernetes